superpay.me 2019-07-17

# SuperPay.Me - Privacy Policy

## How we use and store data

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to let you know what kinds of information we may gather about you, how we may use that information, whether we share that information, and the choices you have regarding our use of that information. 

We process Personal information for certain legitimate business purposes which include some or all of the following:

To be able to participate on our site, you will need to provide us with the following registration information:

Genuine and complete name and address information which is required to ensure your account is genuine and to help prevent fraud.

A valid email which will only be used should we need to contact you to update you on the status of offers, surveys and tickets, to provide useful information on the operation of your account or should we need to contact you directly in relation to an enquiry on your account.We do not send spam, or marketing emails without prior consent.

A username and a password to allow you to log in and operate your account securely.

Details of the payment account you wish to use for withdrawals (eg. Paypal Skrill account information) for us to be able to send payment to you when requested.

Valid Telephone number (no bots) To help prevent fraud and for account enquiries.

Additional security information we will record automatically when logging in:

IP Address

Country location

Internet Service Provider

Browser, and device Information (eg. Internet explorer 11, firefox, iphone)

Date and Time of Log In

Details of where you joined us from if available (referral website, facebook, google etc.)

This security information is used in conjunction with the registration information to complete secondary security checks to ensure we have been provided with genuine information, to make sure you are not breaking any rules or terms of our site and fraud prevention.Examples would be creating duplicate accounts, registering false information, or committing fraud.

Additional verification information we may request

Prior to sending any payments, we may also request verification document(s) to verify your registered information (examples might include a utility bill, drivers license or similar.Any documents you send to us will be dealt with securely, are only used for the purpose of verifying your identify or your age and will be permanently deleted within 24 hours of verification of your account. If a further document is requested we will hold the original document until the second document is received, or up to a maximum of 7 days at which point it will be permanently deleted.You will be able to request separately either via email or support ticket that we delete any document you have sent to us at the first opportunity prior to those timescales.

Documents sent to us can only be accessed by members of staff with authorisation to view that email account. Documents may be run through additional security checks (eg. Reverse image searches) to ensure they are genuine.

Documents are not shared with any third parties and are only made available to authorised staff at 99 ventures Ltd.

Information in relation to your participation and activity on our site

Details of surveys, offers, trials etc. attempted, credited and appropriate rewards for those.

A running account balance in points and cash.

Details of any withdrawals and the payment accounts used.

Details of any support tickets you have raised with us, and our responses.

Details of any account changes such as updates to your address, email account.

Details of referrals who have joined as a result of you sharing your personal referral link.

We store your personal data as securely as we can on secure servers. All reasonable steps necessary to ensure your data is adequately protected and processed in line with this privacy notice.

We DO NOT pass your personal data to third parties, unless you specifically ask us to for a particular purpose (e.g. a competition), we have reason to do so as part of an investigation, as part of our site process in crediting your account or as required by law.

We may be required to share some information from your account with our third party advertisers and survey providers in order to assist with certain aspects of the functionality of the site. For example, we need to pass details of your username as part of the process for accessing surveys in order they are able to send a credit for succesfully completed surveys and offers to your account with us. There may also be an enquiry relating to non-crediting, or fraud where we need to able to confirm certain information in order to deal with that situation. Any information shared is limited to what is required to ensure the smooth operating of the crediting process or to establish he facts relating to the issue being investigated.

In instances where we suspect there may be a breach of rules, then as part of our investigation we may share the information we collect with regulatory authorities, relevant bodies, advertising networks and in exceptional circumstances, relevant 3rd parties, in order to protect the site and it's members from potential fraudulent activity.

We do not send junk mail (or spam). We send occasional site updates by email, and you can choose the type of mailings you receive by editing your profile. 

Information Requests

Users may raise a support ticket to request to see any information that we hold. This may include transaction information, account totals, contact details and other information we hold as indicated in our privacy policy. Users will receive the requested information within 14 days of the request. Click Here to raise a support ticket.

Delete Requests

Users of our site can raise a support ticket to request that details of their account and any related information we hold to be removed permanently from our site.Any valid requests will be dealt with within 24 hours and all details will be permanently removed. Click Here to raise a support ticket for a deletion request.

Where possible, accounts will be deleted permanently.Where there has been actual activity on your account, for example you have received a payment from us, or participated in offers, then we will mark your account deleted and cease any further communication, however necessary information relating to your account and activity would be retained for as long as necessary on our system.

Where there has been evidence of a breach of our terms, potential fraudulent activity or any similar offences then we would be unable to process a delete request at that time.The information will be held indefinitely, or until such time that we are satisfied that there has been no breach of rules, fraudulent activity or further threat to our site. In instances where instant deletion cannot be processed immediately, users can resubmit a request to delete their account every 30 days for review. To resubmit your deletion request, send an email to support (at) superpay.me. In circumstances where excessive requests are received, a permanent block on requests may be implemented.

If you feel Superpay.me is not following its stated privacy policy, then you may inform us through our Support Ticket Page. You may also report any potential concerns to the ICO - <https://ico.org.uk/concerns/>

Cookies

We recommend that all users enable cookies in their internet browsers in order to make full use of the site and in order to ensure that any transactions on third party sites are recorded. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive and they are used to record how you navigate this website on each visit. The information cannot be seen by any other websites (so the information is secure) and is used by us to provide features to aid the use of our services. If users do not have cookies enabled, it is likely that third-party retailers will not record some of their transactions.
